Inventory of the BBC World Service Vietnamese radio broadcast recordings
Hoover Institution Archives
- Sound recordings, 1969, 1973-2004; 655 sound tape reels (Box 3-11, digital files)
  - Rock and Roll Years: 1969, 3 March 1995 (Tape 313)
    Summary: music, Rock and Roll, 22:50 minutes. Use copy reference number: 74E2EC78_RockandRoll1969
  - Rock and Roll Years: 1970, 12 April 1995 (Tape 314)
    Summary: music, Rock and Roll, 20:00 minutes. Use copy reference number: F4FDDAC0_RockandRoll1970
  - Rock and Roll Years: 1971, 19 April 1995 (Tape 315)
    Summary: music, Rock and Roll, 19:40 minutes. Use copy reference number: 3524013E_RockandRoll1971
  - Rock and Roll Years: 1972, 26 April 1995 (Tape 316)
    Summary: music, Rock and Roll, 21:12 minutes. Use copy reference number: F546A6D8_RockandRoll1972
  - Rock and Roll Years: 1973, 5 May 1995 (Tape 317)
    Summary: music, Rock and Roll, 20:16 minutes. Use copy reference number: F55852C7_RockandRoll1973
  - Rock and Roll Years: 1974, 10 May 1995 (Tape 318)
    Summary: music, Rock and Roll, 22:25 minutes. Use copy reference number: B61AC1B1_RockandRoll1974
  - Rock and Roll Years: 1975, 19 May 1995 (Tape 319)
    Summary: music, Rock and Roll, 19:35 minutes. Use copy reference number: 36554E08_RockandRoll1975
  - Viet Classical Music #4, 20 January 1982 (Tape 320)
    Summary: music, folk music, 13:10 minutes.
  - Viet Classical Music #5, 24 February 1982 (Tape 321)
    Summary: music, folk music, 14:10 minutes.
  - Viet Classical Music#6, 4 February 1982 (Tape 322)
  - Viet Classica Music #7, 11 February 1982 (Tape 323)
  - Viet Classical Music #8, 11 February 1982 (Tape 324)
    Summary: music, folk music, 12:45 minutes.
  - Viet Classical Music #9, 28 February 1982 (Tape 325)
    Summary: music, folk music, 14:30 minutes.
  - Viet Classical Music #10, 28 February 1982 (Tape 326)
    Summary: music, folk music, 13:55 minutes.
  - Viet Classical Music #12, 11 March 1982 (Tape 327)
    Summary: music, folk music, 15:15 minutes.
  - Bach Yen 1 (Tape 328)
    Summary: music. Use copy reference number: F675FCC0_BachYen1
  - Bach Yen 2 (Tape 329)
    Summary: music. Use copy reference number: 36B4DB35_BachYen2
  - Ngheu So Oc Hen 1, 26 December 1997 (Tape 335)
    Summary: music, drama, 24:40 minutes. Use copy reference number: 77420479_NgheuSoOcHen1
  - Ngheu So Oc Hen 2, 26 December 1997 (Tape 336)
    Summary: music, drama, 24:25 minutes. Use copy reference number: 37552C07_NgheuSoOcHen2
  - My Linh Interview (Tape 337)
    Summary: music, My Linh. Use copy reference number: 76E1A151_InterviewMyLinh
  - Bao Ninh, 27 May 1995 (Tape 339)
    Summary: writers, Bao Ninh. Use copy reference number: FA5479DD_BuiDucAnh
  - A Journey (Tape 351)
  - A Journey: Part 1, 16 April 1990 (Tape 352)
    18:59 minutes. Use copy reference number: D5E465DF_AJourney1
  - A Journey: Part 2, 23 April 1990 (Tape 353)
    19:51 minutes. Use copy reference number: C5F7E58E_AJourney2
  - A Journey: Part 3, 30 April 1990 (Tape 354)
    21:00 minutes.
  - A Journey: Part 4, 8 May 1990 (Tape 355)
    21:25 minutes. Use copy reference number: 560E495B_AJourney4
  - A Hundred Years of Ho Chi Minh's Birthday, 14 May 1990 (Tape 356)
    20:30 minutes. Use copy reference number: 76248331_HoChiMinhBirthday
  - Nhac Thieu So Mien Bac, 19 March 1982 (Tape 371)
  - Anatomy of Leadership 1, 20 June 1996 (Tape 400)
    21:30 minutes.
  - Anatomy of Leadership 2, 12 June 1996 (Tape 401)
    20:47 minutes. Use copy reference number: F5088F3B_AnatomyofLeadership2
  - Anatomy of Leadership, 7 June 1996 (Tape 402)
    19:40 minutes. Use copy reference number: C637358D_AnatomyofLeadership0
  - English Literature, 20 March 1994 (Tape 403)
    20:00 minutes. Use copy reference number: F64A26F4_EnglishLiterature1
  - English Literature 2, 27 March 1994 (Tape 404)
    19:04 minutes. Use copy reference number: 665A7123_EnglishLiterature2
  - English Literature 3, 3 April 1994 (Tape 405)
    Use copy reference number: C668528F_EnglishLiterature3
  - English Literature 4, 10 April 1994 (Tape 406)
    20:12 minutes. Use copy reference number: D67A90D9_EnglishLiterature4
  - English Literature 5, 17 April 1994 (Tape 407)
    17:42 minutes. Use copy reference number: 6688B629_EnglishLiterature5
  - English Literature 6, 24 April 1994 (Tape 408)
    19:15 minutes. Use copy reference number: 46985C4D_EnglishLiterature6
  - English Literature 7, 1 May 1994 (Tape 409)
    19:37 minutes. Use copy reference number: 46A75108_EnglishLiterature7
  - English Literature 8, 8 May 1994 (Tape 410)
    19:10 minutes. Use copy reference number: E6D2B5AC_EnglishLiterature8
  - English Literature 9, 15 May 1994 (Tape 411)
    19:00 minutes. Use copy reference number: C6EBC782_EnglishLiterature9
  - English Literature 10, 22 May 1994 (Tape 412)
    18:40 minutes. Use copy reference number: D700BB9E_EnglishLiterature10
  - Drugs: Fatal Attraction 1, 5 October 1997 (Tape 426)
    19:07 minutes.
  - Drugs: Fatal Attraction 2, 12 October 1997 (Tape 427)
    20:08 minutes.
  - Drugs: Fatal Attraction 3, 19 October 1997 (Tape 428)
    20:20 minutes.
  - Drugs: Fatal Attraction 4, 26 October 1997 (Tape 429)
    20:40 minutes.
  - Drugs: Fatal Attraction 5, 2 November 1997 (Tape 430)
    19:50 minutes.
  - Vietnam: Social and Political Change, 1 July 1997 (Tape 439)
    18:00 minutes. Use copy reference number: F716FCB8_VietnamSocialandPoliticalChange1
  - Vietnam: Social and Political Change, 18 July 1997 (Tape 440)
    19:15 minutes. Use copy reference number: C72833C7_VietnamSocialandPoliticalChange2
  - Thailand Sunday Special, 16 May 1997 (Tape 444)
    18:35 minutes.
  - Burma Sunday Special (Tape 445)
    19:19 minutes. Use copy reference number: 773C9839_BurmaSundaySpecial
  - Eastern Europe: Poland, 4 April 1996 (Tape 446)
    18:20 minutes. Use copy reference number: 674E4167_EasternEuropePoland
  - Hungary, 10 April 1996 (Tape 447)
    19:20 minutes. Use copy reference number: 5760655D_Hungary
  - Viet Community: Hungary, 11 May 1996 (Tape 448)
    10:44 minutes. Use copy reference number: E76EC3E8_VietCommunityHungary
  - Eastern Europe 3, 18 April 1996 (Tape 449)
    19:21 minutes. Use copy reference number: D780D8DD_EasternEurope3
  - Eastern Europe 4, 25 April 1996 (Tape 450)
    19:24 minutes. Use copy reference number: 4796F647_EasternEurope4
  - Eastern Europe 4 (Tape 451)
    19:17 minutes. Use copy reference number: 67A6F92C_EasternEurope4-2
  - Viet Community: Bulgaria (Tape 452)
    12:40 minutes. Use copy reference number: E7B536A0_VietCommunityBulgaria
  - Viet Community: Poland, 2 May 1996 (Tape 453)
    11:30 minutes. Use copy reference number: 77CEEA73_VietCommunityPoland
  - Kosovo: Seeds of Conflict 1, 14 October 2000 (Tape 469)
    20:00 minutes. Use copy reference number: D7E61191_KosovoSeedsofConflict1
  - Kosovo: Seeds of Conflict 1, 14 October 2000 (Tape 470)
    1:00 minutes. Use copy reference number: E7FAC2E9_KosovoSeedsofConflict2
  - Kosovo: Seeds of Conflict 2, 21 October 2000 (Tape 471)
    Use copy reference number: D80CA9D6_KosovoSeedsofConflict3
  - Kosovo: Seeds of Conflict 2, 21 October 2000 (Tape 472)
    0:40 minutes. Use copy reference number: 5814B25C_KosovoSeedsofConflict4
  - Kosovo: Seeds of Conflict 3, 28 October 2000 (Tape 473)
    20:00 minutes. Use copy reference number: D82244D7_KosovoSeedsofConflict5
  - Kosovo: Seeds of Conflict 3, 28 October 2000 (Tape 474)
    0:40 minutes. Use copy reference number: 4834340D_KosovoSeedsofConflict6
  - Freedom's Battle 1, 4 November 2000 (Tape 475)
    20:00 minutes. Use copy reference number: 78466D35_FreedomsBattle1
  - Freedom's Battle 1, 4 November 2000 (Tape 476)
    0:50 minutes. Use copy reference number: E857E7E3_FreedomsBattle2
  - Freedom's Battle 2, 11 November 2000 (Tape 477)
    21:00 minutes. Use copy reference number: D8685F99_FreedomsBattle3
  - Freedom's Battle 2, 11 November 2000 (Tape 478)
    0:40 minutes. Use copy reference number: 586DC758_FreedomsBattle4
  - Freedom's Battle 3, 2 December 2000 (Tape 479)
    20:00 minutes. Use copy reference number: E87BA8EB_FreedomsBattle5
  - Freedom's Battle 3, 2 December 2000 (Tape 480)
    0:40 minutes. Use copy reference number: 7883413D_FreedomsBattle6
  - Freedom's Battle 4, 9 December 2000 (Tape 481)
    20:00 minutes. Use copy reference number: 589AF21C_FreedomsBattle7
  - Freedom's Battle 4, 9 December 2000 (Tape 482)
    0:40 minutes. Use copy reference number: 48A0794C_FreedomsBattle8
  - Freedom's Battle 5, 16 December 2000 (Tape 483)
    18:56 minutes. Use copy reference number: F8AF66B6_FreedomsBattle9
  - Freedom's Battle 6, 23 December 2000 (Tape 484)
    20:03 minutes. Use copy reference number: D8BD5799_FreedomsBattle10
  - Freedom's Battle 6, 23 December 2000 (Tape 485)
    1:08 minutes. Use copy reference number: F8C318FF_FreedomsBattle11
  - Animal Farm, 28 June 2003 (Tape 491)
    22:00 minutes. Use copy reference number: 78D2FD77_AnimalFarm
  - Princess September, 16 December 1985 (Tape 492)
    18:23 minutes. Use copy reference number: C8E37184_PrincessSeptember
  - 1984 Part 1, 22 March 1984 (Tape 493)
    16:50 minutes. Use copy reference number: D8EF569F_1984Part1
  - 1984 Part 5, 3 May 1984 (Tape 494)
    14:00 minutes. Use copy reference number: 6900836C_1984Part2
  - The Sword and the Stone, 5 December 1978 (Tape 495)
    19:10 minutes. Use copy reference number: F90E3ABC_TheSwordandtheStone
  - Gia Biet Mua Nang (Tape 496)
    Summary: Vo Phien, 12:00 minutes. Use copy reference number: E9229FAA_GiaBietMuaNang
  - Mot Mua Xuan An Lanh, 11 December 1993 (Tape 497)
    Summary: Vo Phien, 12:42 minutes. Use copy reference number: D93045D8_MotMuaXuanAnLanh
  - Mot Mua Thu (Tape 498)
    Summary: Vo Phien, 10:05 minutes. Use copy reference number: F93D86B9_MotMuaThu
  - Loi Thoi Gian 1 (Tape 499)
    Summary: Nguyen Thi Ngoc Nhung, 13:25 minutes. Use copy reference number: 5948D11D_LoiThoiGian1
  - Loi Thoi Gian 2 (Tape 500)
    Summary: Nguyen Thi Ngoc Nhung, 8:15 minutes. Use copy reference number: F9530DF6_LoiThoiGian2
  - Santa Ana Mot Ngay Thang 5 (Tape 501)
    Summary: Nguyen Thi Qua, 10:25 minutes. Use copy reference number: 77B0F859_SantaAnaMotNgayThang5
  - Viet Novels (Tape 503)
    13:25 minutes. Use copy reference number: B7BDCFA8_VietNovels
  - The Chrysalids 1, 20 September 1985 (Tape 504)
    12:03 minutes. Use copy reference number: F96144FF_TheChrysalids1
  - The Chrysalids 2, 20 September 1985 (Tape 505)
    10:42 minutes. Use copy reference number: E96EDFAA_TheChrysalids2
  - The Chrysalids 3, 21 September 1985 (Tape 506)
    12:38 minutes. Use copy reference number: 597A2E18_TheChrysalids3
  - The Chrysalids 4, 21 October 1985 (Tape 507)
    10:49 minutes. Use copy reference number: 6985F827_TheChrysalids4
  - The Chrysalids 5, 24 October 1985 (Tape 508)
    12:30 minutes. Use copy reference number: 7D777B7E_TheChrysalids5
  - The Chrysalids 6, 29 October 1985 (Tape 509)
    13:25 minutes. Use copy reference number: FD9AB9D7_TheChrysalids6
  - The Chrysalids 7, 5 November 1985 (Tape 510)
    12:20 minutes. Use copy reference number: F63C923C_TheChrysalids7
  - The Chrysalids 8, 5 November 1985 (Tape 511)
    13:37 minutes. Use copy reference number: C6E2A308_TheChrysalids8
  - The Chrysalids 9, 19 November 1985 (Tape 512)
    13:15 minutes. Use copy reference number: D719EB1F_TheChrysalids9
  - Bui Tin Interview, 28 November 1990 (Tape 513)
    Summary: Bui Tin, 17:35 minutes. Use copy reference number: B9126394_BuiTin
  - Bui Tin 1, 28 November 1990 (Tape 514)
    Summary: Bui Tin, 22:00 minutes. Use copy reference number: EA67F56A_BuiTin1
  - Bui Tin 2, 1 December 1990 (Tape 515)
    Summary: Bui Tin, 18:22 minutes. Use copy reference number: DA93EB5D_BuiTin2
  - Bui Tin 3, 2 December 1990 (Tape 516)
    Summary: Bui Tin, 7:40 minutes. Use copy reference number: BDC5E397_BuiTin3
  - Bui Tin 4, 8 December 1990 (Tape 517)
    Summary: Bui Tin, 18:15 minutes. Use copy reference number: CAB63D84_BuiTin4
  - Bui Tin 5, 9 December 1990 (Tape 518)
    Summary: Bui Tin, 6:35 minutes. Use copy reference number: FACE5BF2_BuiTin5
  - Bui Tin 6, 15 December 1990 (Tape 519)
    Summary: Bui Tin, 19:30 minutes. Use copy reference number: 49953145_BuiTin6
  - Bui Tin 7, 16 December 1990 (Tape 520)
    Summary: Bui Tin, 7:10 minutes. Use copy reference number: D9A1339A_BuiTin7
  - Bui Tin 8, 22 December 1990 (Tape 521)
    Summary: Bui Tin, 17:28 minutes. Use copy reference number: 59AF6A18_BuiTin8
  - Bui Tin 9, 23 December 1990 (Tape 522)
    Summary: Bui Tin, 6:30 minutes. Use copy reference number: 69B87868_BuiTin9
  - Bui Tin 10, 29 December 1990 (Tape 523)
    Summary: Bui Tin, 17:35 minutes. Use copy reference number: E9C5DFA9_BuiTin10
  - Bui Tin 11, 5 January 1991 (Tape 524)
    Summary: Bui Tin, 17:50 minutes. Use copy reference number: D9D17EDF_BuiTin11
  - Bui Tin 12, 6 January 1991 (Tape 525)
    Summary: Bui Tin, 6:05 minutes. Use copy reference number: 49D9E103_BuiTin12
  - Bui Tin 13, 13 January 1991 (Tape 526)
    Summary: Bui Tin, 18:30 minutes. Use copy reference number: B87B4714_BuiTin13
  - Bui Tin 14, 13 January 1991 (Tape 527)
    Summary: Bui Tin, 5:45 minutes. Use copy reference number: B8AABB34_BuiTin14
  - Bui Tin 15, 19 January 1991 (Tape 528)
    Summary: Bui Tin, 7:30 minutes. Use copy reference number: B8BDFE1C_BuiTin15
  - Bui Tin 16, 20 January 1991 (Tape 529)
    Summary: Bui Tin, 6:55 minutes. Use copy reference number: B8DB3D9C_BuiTin16
  - Bui Tin 17, 26 January 1991 (Tape 530)
    Summary: Bui Tin, 13:27 minutes. Use copy reference number: E8ED0C66_BuiTin17
  - Interview Bui Tin, 23 February 1991 (Tape 531)
    Summary: Bui Tin, 17:52 minutes. Use copy reference number: B9040F99_InterviewBuiTin
  - Bui Tin, 9 February 1991 (Tape 532)
    Summary: Bui Tin, 15:05 minutes. Use copy reference number: DA3D6153_BuiTin0
  - Wild Swans 1, 5 April 1994 (Tape 553)
    18:25 minutes. Use copy reference number: B9495F3B_WildSwans1
  - Wild Swans 9, 11 June 1994 (Tape 554)
    20:19 minutes. Use copy reference number: B9641B9D_WildSwans9
  - Wild Swans 11, 5 June 1994 (Tape 555)
    20:24 minutes. Use copy reference number: B974411F_WildSwans11
  - Wild Swans 14, 5 July 1994 (Tape 556)
    20:07 minutes. Use copy reference number: A98D860D_WildSwans14
  - Wild Swans 17, 6 August 1994 (Tape 557)
    20:14 minutes. Use copy reference number: A99C7F0D_WildSwans17
  - Wild Swans 21, 3 September 1994 (Tape 558)
    20:00 minutes. Use copy reference number: BE04F8A3_WildSwans21
  - Wild Swans 23, 17 September 1994 (Tape 559)
    17:30 minutes. Use copy reference number: A9AB30A0_WildSwans23
  - Special Program on Ho Chi Minh, 11 May 1990 (Tape 573)
    Summary: Ho Chi Minh. Use copy reference number: FE504EE4_HoChiMinh
  - Far Eastern Concert (Tape 578)
    Use copy reference number: BE6E0C88_FarEasternConcert
  - Tran Quang Hai and Bach Yen Concert A (Tape 579)
    Use copy reference number: FEC916EC_TranQuangHaiandBachYenA
  - Tran Quang Hai and Bach Yen Concert B (Tape 580)
    Use copy reference number: BF092585_TranQuangHaiandBachYenB
  - Interview with South Vietnam Foreign Minister (Tape 605)
    7:50 minutes. Use copy reference number: F9DD7753_InterviewSouth VietnamForeignMinister
  - Interview Minister Nguyen Van Bac, 1 August 1974 (Tape 607)
    Use copy reference number: E9F071E8_InterviewNguyenVanBac
  - Dong Au (Tape 610)
    Use copy reference number: EA223AEB_DongAu
  - 1. Nguyen Phuc Vinh Tung (Tape 611)
    Summary: 60 or over royal, 7:10 minutes. Use copy reference number: BA2E6FBE_NguyenPhucVinhTung
  - 2. Phan Trung Chanh (Tape 612)
    Summary: 33 year old male, 4:30 minutes. Use copy reference number: EA39EB4B_PhanTrungChanh
  - 3. Duong Viet Trinh (Tape 613)
    Summary: 24 year old beautitian from Tay Ninh, 6:20 minutes. Use copy reference number: FA43CCD7_DuongVietTrinh
  - 4. Bui Duc Anh (Tape 614)
    Summary: 21 year old male electrician from Karlsruhe Germany, 7:00 minutes. Use copy reference number: FA5479DD_BuiDucAnh
  - 5. Nguyen Quang (Tape 615)
    Summary: 55 year old male oil expert from Scandinavia, 5:30 minutes. Use copy reference number: EA6FE7C2_NguyenQuang
  - 6. Nguyen Dang Khoa (Tape 616)
    Summary: 33 year old male computer programmer in Saigon, 7:15 minutes. Use copy reference number: FA79CDF9_NguyenDangKhoa
  - 7. To Huy Thong (Tape 617)
    Summary: Musical Instrument seller in Saigon, 7:20 minutes. Use copy reference number: AA87BE00_ToHuyThong
  - 21. Quach Minh Man (Tape 618)
    Summary: 66 year old male from Soc Trang, 5:15 minutes. Use copy reference number: EA945ECF_QuachMinhMan
  - 22. Le Thanh Binh (Tape 619)
    Summary: 34 year old teacher in Kontum, 7:05 minutes. Use copy reference number: AA9E2B04_LeThanhBinh
  - 23. Nguyen Thi My (Tape 620)
    Summary: 50 year old teacher from Ben Tre, 7:15 minutes. Use copy reference number: AAA7138C_NguyenThiMy
  - 24. Thai Van Dung (Tape 621)
    Summary: 30 year old male food seller, 6:00 minutes. Use copy reference number: BAB3651C_ThaiVanDung
  - 25. Nguyen Quang Ru (Tape 622)
    Summary: 79 year old male, 5:10 minutes. Use copy reference number: FAD9E450_NguyenQuangRu
  - 26. Pham Quoc Trieu (Tape 623)
    Summary: 79 year old former soldier, 4:10 minutes. Use copy reference number: AAF10F02_PhamQuocTrieu
  - 27. Em Dong (Tape 624)
    6:00 minutes. Use copy reference number: FB3F8C58_EmDong
  - 28. Trinh Thi Van (Tape 625)
    5:15 minutes. Use copy reference number: FB4A435C_TrinhThiVan
  - 34. Pham Ngoc Lan (Tape 626)
    Summary: 60 year old amateur musician in San Jose, 6:30 minutes. Use copy reference number: 3F393A28_34PhamNgocLan
  - 35. Trang Thanh Truc (Tape 627)
    Summary: 40 year old songwriter in Paris, 6:40 minutes. Use copy reference number: 7F230073_35ThangThanhTruc
  - 36. Nguyen Long (Tape 628)
    Summary: expatriate in Denver, 7:00 minutes. Use copy reference number: FF5522E3_36NguyenLong
  - 37. Nguyen Quoc Bao (Tape 629)
    Summary: expatriate in Alaska, 5:15 minutes. Use copy reference number: 3F683516_37NguyenQuocBao
  - 38. Nguyen Viet Son (Tape 630)
    Summary: aspirant journalist, 6:20 minutes. Use copy reference number: 3F82363A_38NguyenVietSon
  - 39. Nguyen Ngoc Minh Tan (Tape 631)
    Summary: 19 year old male student in New Zealand, 6:30 minutes. Use copy reference number: FB2E76BC_39NguyenNgocMinhTan
  - 40. Vu Van Van (Tape 632)
    Summary: 66 year old male from Norway, 5:30 minutes. Use copy reference number: FF24F77C_VuVanVan
  - 41. Nguyen Gia Bao (Tape 633)
    Summary: 21 year old male student from Lyon, 8:20 minutes. Use copy reference number: FB4F22BA_41NguyenGiaBao
  - 42. Dang Trong Dung (Tape 634)
    Summary: 54 year old lawyer from HCM, 6:00 minutes. Use copy reference number: FF374FDD_DangTrongDung
  - 43. Phan Tuan Long (Tape 635)
    Summary: interpreter living in Bac Giang, 4:50 minutes. Use copy reference number: AF40A82F_PhanTuanLong
  - 44. Phan Minh Tan (Tape 636)
    Summary: 40 year old male in U.S. from Sweden, 7:00 minutes. Use copy reference number: FF4C4453_PhanMinhTan
  - 45. Do Xuan Que (Tape 637)
    Summary: priest from HCM, 7:10 minutes. Use copy reference number: AF560888_DoXuanQue
  - 46. Soeur Hong Quy (Tape 638)
    8:40 minutes. Use copy reference number: FF5E8454_SoeurHongQuy
  - 47. Tran Quang Hoan (Tape 639)
    Summary: 22 year old male student from Nam Dinh, 6:15 minutes. Use copy reference number: BF687618_TranQuangHoan
  - 48. Nguyen Bich Ngoc (Tape 640)
    Summary: 21 year old student, 6:30 minutes. Use copy reference number: EF84BD4D_NguyenBichNgoc
  - 49. Ngo Quang Hung (Tape 641)
    Summary: 19 year old male student, 5:30 minutes. Use copy reference number: BF8CD5B5_NgoQuangHung
  - 50. Nguyen Van Trong (Tape 642)
    Summary: 37 year old male fish sauce manufacturer in Phan Thiet, 7:00 minutes. Use copy reference number: FF955055_NguyenVanTrong
  - Nam Dao 1 (Tape 643)
    Use copy reference number: AFA81404_NamDao1
  - Nam Dao 2 (Tape 644)
    Use copy reference number: EFC6AE63_NamDao2
  - Globalization 1 (Tape 645)
    Use copy reference number: EFD1F8C8_Globalization1
  - Globalization 2 (Tape 646)
    Use copy reference number: BFDA8B9B_Globalization2
  - Tran Duc Quyen, Kuala Lumpur, 9 February 2004 (Tape 647)
    6:00 minutes. Use copy reference number: BFE28BBC_TranDucQuyen
  - Music Request 1, 10 February 2004 (Tape 648)
    4:40 minutes. Use copy reference number: BFEA099A_MusicRequest1
  - Music Request 2, 11 February 2004 (Tape 649)
    4:45 minutes. Use copy reference number: D291EFD5_Musicrequest2, EFF3F54D_MusicRequest2
  - Music Request 3, 12 February 2004 (Tape 650)
    5:25 minutes. Use copy reference number: BFFF4118_MusicRequest3
  - Music Request 4, 13 February 2004 (Tape 651)
    5:00 minutes. Use copy reference number: F008CFD7_MusicRequest4
  - Arts in Action, 24 February 2001 (Tape 652)
    8:00 minutes. Use copy reference number: F01B0ED3_ArtsinAction1
  - Arts in Action, 3 March 2001 (Tape 653)
    8:00 minutes. Use copy reference number: F038954C_ArtsinAction2
  - Science Week 51, 20 December 2002 (Tape 654)
    10:59 minutes. Use copy reference number: F13686D9_ScienceWeek51
  - Giang Special (Tape 655)
    Use copy reference number: F14CE5DE_GiangSpecial